JEROME PETER G. FLORES

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

09760422995

jpeterflores.24@gmail.com

Cainta Rizal

RELEVANT LINKS

https://github.com/FloresJerome

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jerome-flores-19ab57277

KEY SKILLS

Front-End: HTML, CSS, Javascript/ReactJS

Back-End: PHP (Laravel)

Database: MySQL, Vercel

Others: Microsoft Word/Excel, Canva

SOFT SKILLS

- . Communicating Skills
- Teamwork
- · Self Learning
- · Critical Thinker
- Adaptability
- **Emotional Intelligence**
- Time Management

EDUCATION

2017-2020

Rizal Technological University

Bachelor of Science in Industrial Technology

2012-2015

Rizal Technological University

Diploma in Electrical Engineering Technology.

PROFILE

I am a web developer who works hard, self-motivated, trustworthy, and responsible. I have experience working in teams and can handle any difficult circumstances. I can work well on my own initiative as well as in a collaborative setting. I can complete tasks quickly and accurately under pressure.

WORK EXPERIENCE

System Integrator

OptionSpec Corp.

2017 - 2023

- · Integrating several system into one system or in app.
- Testing the network and automation equipment to ensure effectiveness.
- Connecting the systems to an internet network to work it remotely.
- · System design and troubleshooting.
- Knowledgeable in CCTV, Wi-fi Access point, Door Access Control, Intercom System and Smart Home Automation

Construction Project Coordinator

Hospitality Technology Trends Phils

2015 - 2016

- Collecting data and tracking project accomplishment.
- providing status updates and progress reports.
- Supervising and monitoring group of people.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

KodeGo - Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

Foodie Express

May 2023

https://github.com/Kashea/Aramis

- An e-commerce food ordering/delivery website. Customers can browse a digital menu in a website and place and pay for their food orders online.
- Tools used: CSS, Bootstrap, ReactJS, Laravel.

KodeGo - Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

April 2023 Gizmotronix

https://github.com/FloresJerome/Gizmotronix-ecommerce

- An e-commerce smartphone online shop. This online ordering system's primary objective is to increase client convenience.
- Tools used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript.